First up, here are
supplemental funds for Sebas.
Next, here is the reconstruction
assistance and equipment fund
for the Lizard Man villages.
That leaves...
That's all there is?!
It's not enough.
There's nowhere near enough money!
I wonder if it would be best
to get some merchant to sponsor me.
No, I have to avoid the impression
that the adventurer Momon
is only in it for the money.
Still, I really need the cash...
Enter.
Is something wrong, Nabe?
Yes, Mr. Momon...
She's still doing it off and on--
it has become what I can
only describe as a verbal tic.
Well?
Right. The iron ore that you ordered
from that merchant is ready.
I see. I'll get his payment ready at once.
But why are you ordering it
from so many different sources?
It's an experiment. I'm learning
how the Exchange Box appraises things.
Understood. Then I shall go buy it at once.
Right. And if the situation arises...
you know what to do, right?
I will give safety top priority,
and withdraw with all haste.
I will relocate to the counterfeit Nazarick
that Lord Aura is building,
thereby feeding false information
to the other side.
Very good. By no means
take any routes with large crowds,
where you may be easily attacked. And even
if you do get bumped by someone,
or someone calls out to you,
do not grievously injure them.
No showering your bloodlust about, either.
And absolutely no calling humans "worms."
After all, we are Momon and Nabe,
hailed as high-ranking
raven black adventurers.
Right.
Hmm. Okay, off you go, Nabe.
Ugh... Expenses always come
when you're out of money, huh?
Why don't you call it a day?
Lord Stronoff...
There's no point in overdoing it, Climb.
You are quite right.
My word,
if you really believe that,
I wish you wouldn't make me
repeat myself over and over again.
I am terribly sorry.
What do you say to a little practice match?
But, sir...
Just recently, I was shown how callow I am.
I'd like to train with someone
who has a little resilience.
Who, you, Lord Stronoff?
Yeah. If a merciful magic caster
hadn't come to my aid,
I probably wouldn't
be standing here right now.
Who is this magic caster?
Ains Ooal Gown--
someone who, most likely,
could give that freakish wizard
from the Baharuth Empire
a run for his money.
At least, that's what I think of him.
I will commit the gentleman's name to memory.
So then, are you sure you wish to train me?
Not training, just practicing
with our swords.
Whether or not you take
anything away from it is up to you.
Now, come at me like this is actual combat.
Aren't you going?
If not, I'll take the fight... to you!
Just because a sword is all I'm carrying
doesn't mean you should
focus all your attention on it.
Otherwise, you could
get kicked like you just did.
Right.
Ho...
A typical soldier would be
finished after one of those.
I have to become stronger than I am.
So I can keep Princess Renner safe.
Mm-hmm. Bring it on, Climb!
Unfortunately for you, this will end up
the same way as last time...!
Martial Art! Fortress!
You were waiting for that?!
Yes!
Martial Art!
Slash!
Bravo. Now I'm going to
take this a bit more seriously.
Please do!
How about it?
I was trying not to smash or
fracture anything while swinging at you.
Nothing worse than a bruise...
No problem at all...
You'll be heading off
to bodyguard the princess now, right?
Yes, sir...
In that case, I'll give this to you.
Thank you very much.
You really are amazing. How did you...
If you're asking how I got so strong,
I don't have a good answer.
I simply happen to have a talent for it.
However, Climb, you're cut out
for the kind of fighting I do.
I... am?
Yeah. Those who receive formal training...
...can't help but focus
on fighting with their swords,
but I don't see that as a good thing.
Realizing that the sword
is just one means of attacking,
and using your hands and feet
in your method of fighting
are what will really be
of use to you in combat.
Of course, that's more a style
for mud-ridden adventurers.
Thank you for your
pointers today, Lord Stronoff.
That strike from above was a pretty good one.
Although, you should also think about
what you're going to do next.
Right! I will!
Head Warrior...
Well, if you will excuse me...
What is it, Vice-Chief?
This is bad, sir.
He's Princess Renner's bodyguard.
If word gets out that he fought the
royal head warrior, and either of you lost,
the Noble Faction will have a field day.
I just wanted to fight someone
who could fight me back for a bit.
Well, I don't think anyone saw you.
He's an orphan whom
the princess took in on a whim.
The nobles' antipathy
toward him is pretty strong,
with him being a boy
from God only knows where.
So, does he show
any promise for improvement?
Nope. No matter how hard he tries,
he's what adventurers
would call "capped at gold."
But while he may be limited by his ability,
he isn't limited by experience.
That's what I think.
That's...
Prince Zanac and Marquis Raeven, isn't it?
Why would Marquis Raeven
of the Noble Faction be with him?
Could he be switching sides
to the Royal Faction?
It wouldn't surprise me
to see Marquis Raeven anywhere.
The man is an opportunist by nature.
He likely has many things
in motion behind the scenes.
Oh my, Climb. On your way
to visit that monster, are you?
Your Highness, with all due respect,
Princess Renner is a person
who could be called a kindhearted,
beautiful treasure of the kingdom.
I wasn't the one here who
just referred to Renner as a monster.
But a treasure?
Erecting facilities for the commoners,
and prohibiting transit tariffs
for adventurers? It's unheard-of.
Your Highness, I believe the measure
that abolished slave trafficking
that was passed the other day
was proposed by Princess Renner.
A rare exception.
But what about other than that?
I have the feeling that she is
acting with the understanding
that what she is doing is impossible.
I am certain that she would not do so!
I see, I see, then would you
tell that monster something for me?
Our elder brother, Barbro,
thinks of her as a political instrument,
but if she will work with
me, the second prince,
he will relieve her of the title of princess,
and grant her some territory
out on the frontiers.
Surely you jest!
I will pretend I did not hear that.
That's a shame.
Ah, I almost forgot.
Marquis Raeven is of the same opinion as me,
and says he considers that
girl to be a monster.
And since we see eye-to-eye,
it seems that our joining forces
was the right call.
Prince Zanac...
Don't worry about it, Marquis Raeven.
Knowing that monster,
I'm sure she already knows our opinion.
Goodness, what is a commoner doing in here?
The princess is quite the fanciful one.
Definitely.
Pardon me.
Morning, Climb.
Good morning,
Princess Renner... Lady Aindra....
Whoops...
Oh, she's one of my team members.
This is Tina.
I beg your pardon. It is a pleasure
to meet you. My name is Climb.
I am extremely pleased
to meet the renowned Lady Tina,
of the adventurers group Blue Rose.
The pleasure's mine.
Thanks for looking out for our fiendish boss.
Climb, why don't you have a seat
before we start talking?
But I am your bodyguard, so...
It makes no difference to me.
Yes, but... Lady Aindra...
I told you before, call me Lakyus.
Because you're so special, Climb.
--Oof...
--Please don't joke like that.
Huh? Joke?
Of course it was.
Now, Climb is special, to be sure,
but he's special because he's yours.
Jeez...
Go on, feel free to sit down, Climb.
That nice tea will get cold.
Let's go back to what
we were talking about before.
About Eight Fingers, right?
You're with me up to the part
where we burned the fields
that were growing the raw materials
for Black Dust, right?
Yes. Lakyus, I really am grateful
to you and your team.
My brother and the nobles do nothing
but quarrel among their factions,
and if they keep allowing Eight Fingers
to secretly do business
behind the scenes of the kingdom,
it will soon fall into ruin,
and the kingdom will
collapse from the inside.
However, I do not have
any influential backing,
nor a military force at my discretion.
Eight Fingers has ties to the nobles--
no, to the royals as well,
and if I'm to fight them,
I have no choice but to turn
to adventurers, such as yourselves.
Enough of that, now. We're friends, right?
Tina, let's have it.
We discovered this at the village
where they were producing Black Dust.
Can you tell what it is?
This is a substitution cipher.
Makes sense. The reason
this was left behind...
...was as a trap? Or for some other reason?
If that were the case, they wouldn't
use something so hard. Mm-hmm.
If that's it, I have a hunch that
cracking this code will be pretty easy.
Unbelievable.
She says that she is powerless to help,
but I don't know anyone else
for whom the word "genius" is a better fit.
I cracked it. It isn't a written order,
but each one of these appear to be
the name of a village or building.
Seven of which are within the capital.
I wonder if these are Black Dust stockpiles,
or other critical sites.
I doubt they would have
anything that important written in code
and left in an ordinary production site.
It's probably bait.
--Bait?
Well, um, Eight Fingers is divided up
into eight different organizations, right?
Such as drugs, slave trafficking,
smuggling, and gambling.
Rumor has it that each section
has its own chief.
Then I believe these are the bases
for those other organizations.
Their goal is to temporarily
draw interest away from themselves.
And they're using
their own partners as the bait?
That underground brothel isn't on here.
What is it?
Begging your pardon,
but thanks to Princess Renner's work,
I thought that such establishments
had been done away with.
Yes, thanks to the slave
trade being abolished.
However, there is still one
Eight Fingers underground brothel
in business in the capital.
Tell me, Renner, what would you say
to Blue Rose raiding the place?
If we can turn up some evidence,
it would strike a powerful blow
against the nobles
who are in bed with Eight Fingers.
But that would create trouble
for your family, the Alveins.
On the other hand, it would be
too much for Climb to handle alone.
I am terribly sorry for my lack of strength.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Climb!
That isn't what I meant by that!
I rely on you most of all, Climb.
I know just how hard you work for me.
Still, don't do anything too foolhardy, okay?
That isn't a request; it's an order.
If anything were to happen to you, I'd...
Ahem... In any case,
while we can't ignore the brothel,
let's first discuss what we're going to do
about the other locations
revealed by the code.
Right. We should take action quickly.
They haven't realized that
we're the ones who attacked the village.
But they have to know that
this information has already gotten out.
Then is it okay if we borrow Climb from you?
I want him to go right away,
and tell Gagaran and the others
that we're going to be making our move.
Understood!
Come to think of it,
Tina's investigation turned up the names
--Look. It sounds like the princess
is about to do something again.
--of several nobles who have dealings
with the slave trade chief, Cocco Doll.
It must be tough for those Blue Rose ladies.
That nobleman's daughter
is currently serving as one of my maids.
Huh? It doesn't seem likely
that she is here just to spy on you, but...
You're right. I'll have to
warn Climb to be careful.
Welcome... back... Lord Sebas...
I'm home, Tuare. I trust there were
no problems with your work?
No... none...
I see. Glad to hear it.
What are we having for dinner today?
A stew... made with... potatoes...
I look forward to it.
Your cooking is tasty, Tuare.
Oh... no...
I mean it. Now, do you
have enough ingredients?
Oh, I will... check later...
Would you like to go shopping together?
No... that's... all right...
Tuare, I understand why you are afraid.
You must be terrified of going outside.
But please rest at ease;
I, Sebas, will protect you.
No matter what peril may befall you,
I will dash them all, and keep you safe.
Tuare, please step forward.
If you are scared,
I do not mind if you close your eyes.
Would you place your trust in me?
Lord Sebas, you are... a rascal...
When you say it like that...
I cannot... say no...
Please do not worry.
I may not look it, but I am plenty strong.
Indeed. There are only 41 others,
and perhaps a few more,
who are stronger than me.
Is that... a lot...?
My lady, I have returned.
Very good, Sebas.
Are you sure we should not inform Lord Ains?
You must be in daily contact with him.
Could you not simply make mention
of the woman when you speak to him?
I have an extremely high regard
for her culinary abilities. Moreover,
it might be seen as odd for only two people
to be living in such a large mansion
as this, might it not?
You are saying that this is
part of a diversionary tactic?
Correct. If I seek permission from
Lord Ains over maintaining our cover,
he will snap at me, and tell me
to think for myself over such a thing.
I am Staffan Havish, a constable
charged with keeping the capital safe.
So, what can I do for you?
There is an establishment--
well, his establishment, as it happens...
Succulent. It is a pleasure to meet you.
I received a report from
his establishment, you see,
that someone carrying a scroll
bearing the seal of the magicians' guild
handed over an inordinate amount of money
and carried off one of
the establishment's employees.
Slave trafficking is prohibited
within the kingdom,
and it sounds as though
this was a violation of that.
Is that so?
Huh?
I will let my butler, Sebas,
deal with this touchy matter.
Sebas, you handle it from here.
Good day, gentlemen.
Now then, in my lady's stead,
I will hear whatever it is you have to say.
Well, from the circumstantial evidence,
it is beyond a doubt
that you have committed a crime,
but the establishment
is willing to offer you clemency.
Naturally, this will incur
consolation payments and commissions.
I see. How much will that cost?
It will be 500 gold coins.
That is extortionate. She
was in a terrible state.
If you were to take her away now,
she might very well die.
You don't say, you don't say.
Well then, until she is done convalescing,
what would you say to loaning us
the lady of your house?
Oh, indeed, your lost income
must be compensated.
Is your excessive lust not a problem for you?
Huh?! How rude of you to mention lust!
This whole law originally
came about at the noble behest
of the eminent Golden Princess, Renner!
You dare to--
Now, now, please calm yourself, Lord Havish.
We will return for your decision
the day after tomorrow.
Will that be all right, Mr. Sebas?
Understood.
What are you going to do?
I think I would like to think this through
over a short stroll outside.
Message.
Is that you, Lord Ains?
Solution? I'm surprised
to have you contact me.
Is there an emergency?
Yes. There is a chance
that Lord Sebas has turned on us.
Hmm. Huh? Eh?! You can't mean it!
Ahem, no more kidding around, Solution.
A declaration like that without
any proof cannot go unanswered.
Is there any?
Yes.